A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Natural and Historic Resources, 2017-2021 (bulk 2018-2021)
Library of Virginia
- Series IV. Records of Meryem Karad, 2017-2019, Extent: 3.5 boxes (Box 8-11)
  - Department of Game and Inland Fisheries (DGIF), 2018-2019 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Environmental Groups contact list, circa 2018 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Chesapeake Bay Commission, 2018 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - University of Virginia (UVA) Idea Fund, Spring Trustee Board Meeting, 2018 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Congressional committees' notes, circa 2019 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Governor's office, staff, and other contact lists, circa 2015-2018 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation (VLCF), 2019 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Department of Historic Resources memorandum, 2018 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Virginia's Emancipation Trail, 2010, 2019 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Sustainable Virginia, circa 2018-2019 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Natural Resources Leadership Institute Think Tank, 2018 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Atlantic Coast Pipeline, 2016-2018 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Mountain Valley Pipeline, 2017 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Atlantic Coast Pipeline, 2018 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Atlantic Coast Pipeline, 2018 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Report to Governor Ralph S. Northam on Executive Order Number Six, by Matthew J. Strickler, 2019 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Monuments Work Group, 2016 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Environment Virginia Symposium Planning, 2019 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Session, Legislative Action Summaries, 2019 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Memorandum of Agreement among Virginia Electric and Power Company, the Virginia State Historic Preservation Office, U.S. Army Corps of Engineers (USACE) Norfolk District, and Advisory Council on Historic Preservation, 2017 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Dupont Settlement memos and announcement remarks, 2017-2018 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Dupont Settlement: USA and Commonwealth of Virginia Secretary of Natural Resources V.E.I. du Pont de Nemours and company, Civil Action No. 5:16-CV-00082, 2017 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Dominion Energy Bill, 2018 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Chesapeake Bay Regulatory and Accountability Program (CBRAP), 2014-2017, 2018 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Memorandums of Agreement for mitigation regarding the Mountain Valley Pipeline and the Atlantic Coast Pipeline, 2017 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Outdoors Foundation (VOF) and the African-American cemeteries, East End and Evergreen, 2015-2016 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Governor Terence R. McAuliffe Meeting with the Virginia Congressional Delegation, 2017 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Molly Ward, Economic Interest Statements, (McAuliffe), 2014-2017 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Decarbonize Virginia Electric Power Generation, (McAuliffe), 2017 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Dominion Virginia Power transmission line across the James River, (McAuliffe), 2016 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Office of the Secretary of the Commonwealth, Modernizing the Bluebook, circa 2018 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - National Climate and Energy Funders Meeting, 2018 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Conservation Cabinet, 2019 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Program of Events at Virginia State Parks, 2018 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Transportation and Climate Initiative, 2019 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Office of the Secretary of Natural Resources itinerary of attended events, January-August, circa 2018-2019 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 2018-2019 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Forever budget, circa 2018-2019 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Legislation, 2018-2019 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Go Green Virginia, 2018 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - 2018 Senate of Virginia contact list, 2018 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Series V. Constituent Correspondence, 2017-2020, Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 11-15)
  The Secretary of Natural and Historic Resources constituent correspondence is focused primarily on the issues surrounding the building of the Atlantic Coast pipeline and the Mountain Valley pipeline. Mailings include Go Green Virginia and Virginia is Not For Pipelines.
  - Virginia is Not for Pipelines postcards, 2018 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Postcards requesting FERC comply with the Endangered Species Act regarding the natural gas pipelines, 2019 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Postcards requesting FERC to comply with the Endangered Species Act regarding the natural gas pipelines, 2019 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Postcards requesting the natural gas pipelines be held to the highest environmental standards, circa 2019 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Postcards requesting the natural gas pipelines be held to the highest environmental standards, circa 2019 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Postcards requesting the natural gas pipelines be held to the highest environmental standards, circa 2019 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Postcards requesting the natural gas pipelines be held to the highest environmental standards, circa 2019 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Postcards regarding the permit for Dominion Power to build compressors in Rockingham County, Virginia, 2018 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Atlantic Coast Pipeline (ACP) and Mountain Valley Pipeline (MVP) presentation, circa 2018-2019 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Atlantic Coast Pipeline (ACP) and Mountain Valley Pipeline (MVP) presentation, circa 2018-2019 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Atlantic Coast Pipeline correspondence from the Jackson River Preservation Association (JRPA), 2018 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Report of the Subcommittee on Economic Development and Natural Resources, 2018 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 2019 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 2020 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Pipeline letters, 2018 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2018 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2018 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 2018 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 2018 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2018 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 2018 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 2018 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2018 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2018 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 2018 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 2018 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2018 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 2017, 2018 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 2018 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2018 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2018 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Thumb-drive, contents currently unknown, circa 2017-2018 (Box 15, Folder 4)